"Tomorrow's weather is better off not known," I say,
So I don't carry an umbrella
Any downpour of tears that may await me
Will be rewritten into the gentlest of lies
The pieces of the sky enclosed within the box
Cannot connect to form the puzzle of the future
Static, spat out from my infinith inference,
Is the logic to deceive God himself,
Bringing us closer to that promised place...
We will open the gate of Zero, still unknown to the universe,
Reducing everything to particles and reassembling it all
Even so, I'll show you I can hold on to this discontinuous consciousness,
And in that hour, in that place, your "time" will begin once more